<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Untitled RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Untitled RSS Feed]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 08:54:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="undefined/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Introducing Me]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>I donot know anyone who has reached the top without hardwork. It will not always get you to the top but would help to get pretty near.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This is me in short. Hardwork, determination and lot of great people are those which helped to me to get till here writing this blog. I know you have not much of an idea but wait, you will get it soon.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I am student from FOSS@Amrita. I am no tech geek, but I love to be good at what I am doing. FOSS@Amrita, a wonderful club where people of same interest in the world of Computers, join in to develop, play and exploit the field of computers to find out what is best for us.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I love to code and solve challenging problems. My personal intersts would be towards areas like Networking and Operating Systems. The best part of being a computer science enthusiast is that we get find multidimensional answers for different problems. I also an active editor to WikiToLearn Community.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Personally, I love to read and talk a lot. Israel-Palestian issue and Rise of ISIS are one of my favourite areas of interests. Moreover, I am hardcore pottermore, who loves be the "girl who lived" with an OCD like Monica Geller. HAHA! You got it I am crazy F.R.I.E.N.D.S fan too. I cannot resist exploring different places and cultures.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Life is full of challenges and these are the few things that helps me keep going with all the happiness, I have!</p>
</div>]]></description><link>undefined/2017/03/11/Introducing-Me.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">undefined/2017/03/11/Introducing-Me.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Haritha Harikumar]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>